const cards = [{
    id: 1,
    front: "Oeufs",
    back: "Eggs",
    difficulty: "medium"
}, {
    id: 2,
    front: "Pain",
    back: "Bread",
    difficulty: "medium"
}, {
    id: 3,
    front: "Croissant",
    back: "croissant",
    difficulty: "easy"
}, {
    id: 4,
    front: "Miel",
    back: "Honey",
    difficulty: "hard"
}, {
    id: 5,
    front: "Pain grillé",
    back: "Toast",
    difficulty: "hard"
}, {
    id: 6,
    front: "Gâteau",
    back: "Cake",
    difficulty: "medium"
}, {
    id: 7,
    front: "Porc",
    back: "Pork",
    difficulty: "easy"
}, {
    id: 8,
    front: "Fromage",
    back: "Cheese",
    difficulty: "easy"
}, {
    id: 9,
    question: "Pomme",
    back: "Apple",
    difficulty: "easy"
}, {
    id: 10,
    question: "Banane",
    back: "Banana",
    difficulty: "easy"
}];

export default cards;